Finding Aid for Blair Moody Papers 1928-1954
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Scrapbooks
  - 1937-1938 (Box 19)
  - 1938-1939 (Box 19)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 19)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 19)
  - 1941-1942 (Box 20)
  - 1942-1943 (Box 20)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 20)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 20)
  - 1945-1946 (Box 21)
  - 1946-1947 (Box 21)
  - 1947 (Box 21)
  - 1947-1948 (Box 21)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 22)
  - 1949 (Box 22)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 22)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 22)
  - 1951 (Box 22)
  - Scrapbooks of Barron's columns (Box 23)
    - 1936-1940 (Box 23)
    - 1940-1942 (Box 23)
    - 1942-1944 (Box 23)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 23)
    - 1946-1948 (Box 24)
  - Scrapbook of articles concerning Europe, 1947; 3 volumes (Box 24)
  - Appointment books
    - 1946 (Box 24)
    - 1947 (Box 24)
    - 1948 (Box 24)
    - 1950 (Box 24)
    - 1952 (Box 24)
  - Scrapbooks of articles concerning the activities of Detroit soldiers in World War II, 1944; 3 volumes (Box 25)
  - Scrapbook concerning speaking engagements, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Guest register for birthday party, 1952 (Box 25)
  - Scrapbook concerning government finance, undated (Box 25)
  - Newspaper clippings of articles on "The Low-down on Washington,", 1938 (Box 25)
- Sound Recordings
  The Sound Recordings include both sound tapes and sound disks. Beginning in 1946 and continuing through the first few months of 1954, Moody was moderator of "Meet Your Congress, a weekly public affairs program which appeared first on radio and then in the early 1950s on television. Moody liked to refer to the program as a capsule of the best of Congressional debates on the current issues of the day. His guests each week included members of both the House and the Senate as well as an occasional member of the Executive branch or the private sector. The collection of tapes for the program is unfortunately incomplete. There is one tape that can be dated to 1951; the rest date from 1953 to 1954. Of the tapes in the collection, Moody moderated all the programs except for the last three months when his responsibilities were taken over by fellow journalists, Ernest K. Lindley, Charles Lucey, and Roscoe Drummond. The "Meet Your Congress" series of tapes are all 7 inches and play at 7 1/2 ips. A smaller part of the Moody tape collection consists of broadcasts of his "This is Washington" program which was the means he used to report to his constituents on his activities as senator during 1951-52. The collection includes four of these tapes, all from 1951. They are 5 inches and play at 7 1/2 ips. There is finally a speech given by Moody at Laurium Union Hall, October 16, 1952. Moody was then in the midst of what would then be an unsuccessful campaign for reelection.
  The sound disk subseries dates earlier than the sound tapes and include Moody radio broadcasts from 1940 and 1946-1950.
  - Sound tapes
    - Meet Your Congress Program
      - US Foreign Policy and the Firing of General Douglas MacArthur. Panelists: Herbert Lehman, Hubert Humphrey, Robert A. Taft, Homer Capehart, circa 1951 (Box 26)
        (Tape 1)
      - Korean War. Panelists: H. Alexander Smith, William F. Knowland, Paul Douglas, Clinton P. Anderson, May 14, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 2)
      - "A Code of Fair Play for Congressional Investigations." Roscoe Drummond, moderator. Panelists: John J. Sparkman, Paul Douglas., May 30, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 3)
      - International Economics. Panelists: Homer Capehart, Burnet R. Maybank, John D. Dingell, John Leddy?, September 9, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 4)
      - "Foreign Policy." Panelists: Alexander Wiley, Thruston B. Morton, Mike Mansfield, Walter Judd., September 10, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 5)
      - Eisenhower speech on the preservation of liberty. Panelists: Catherine Howard, Harold H. Velde, James E. Murray, Herman Eberharter., September 23, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 6)
      - Farm Prices and Politics. Panelists: Lester C. Hunt, A.L. Miller, Carl Curtis, Wright Patman., October 18, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 7)
      - "Is the Eisenhower Administration Slipping or Gaining?" Panelists: Robert S. Kerr, Craig Hosmer, George A. Smathers, Hugh Scott, November 1, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 8)
      - 1953 Elections and Politics. Panelists: Richard Bolling, Carl Curtis, William Langer, Mike Mansfield., November 8, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 9)
      - "Issues and Politics of the Coming 1954 Session of Congress." Panelists: Albert Gore, Mike Monroney, Clarence J. Brown, Craig Hosmer., November 15, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 10)
      - "Taxes." Panelists: Jacob Javits, Carl Curtis, John D. Dingell, Richard Bolling., November 29, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 11)
      - "Investigating Committees." Panelists: Mike Mansfield, Guy Gillette, Peter Frelinghuysen, Robert W. Kean., December 13, 1953 (Box 26)
        (Tape 12)
      - 1954 Session of Congress. Panelists: Frank Carlson, Henry M. Jackson, H. Alexander Smith, John McCormack., January 10, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 13)
      - Eisenhower's Program in Congress. Panelists: John F. Kennedy, Frank A. Barrett, Mike Monroney, Carl Curtis., January 17, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 14)
      - 1954 Budget. Panelists: George A. Smathers, Hubert Humphrey, Craig Hosmer, Peter Frelinghuysen., January 24, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 15)
      - "The New Look" Military Posture and Budget. Panelists: John Sparkman, Edward Martin, Henry M. Jackson, Clarence J. Brown., January 31, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 16)
      - "The National Economy. "Panelists: Warren Magnuson, Robert W. Kean, Richard Bolling, John M. Vorys., February 7, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 17)
      - "Taxes." Panelists: John Sparkman, Henry M. Jackson, Carl Curtis, Robert W. Kean., February 14, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 18)
      - "Readjustment or recession. "Panelists: Frank A. Barrett, Paul Douglas, George Bender, Wright Patman., February 14, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 19)
      - "Is Our Defense Adequate? "Panelists: James H. Duff, John Sherman Cooper, Mike Monroney, George H. Mahon., February 28, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 20)
      - "Can We Avoid A Major Slump? "Panelists: Frank A. Barrett, Paul Douglas, George Bender, Wright Patman., March 7, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 21)
      - "Should Hawaii and Alaska Become States?" Panelists: William F. Knowland, Warren Magnuson, George Smathers, Joseph R. Farrington., March 14, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 22)
      - "Taxes." Panelists: Paul Douglas, J. William Fulbright, Carl Curtis, Robert W. Kean., March 21, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 23)
      - "New Look" Military Posture. Panelists: Francis Case, Edward Martin, Henry M. Jackson, Samuel W. Yorty., March 28, 1954 (Box 26)
        (Tape 24)
      - "Should the Government Act Now to Reverse the Slump?" Panelists: Frank Carlson, Frank A. Barrett, Herbert Lehman, Richard Bolling., April 4, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 25)
      - Hydrogen Bomb Explosion. Panelists: James H. Duff, Sterling M. Cole, Clinton M. Anderson, Thomas A. Burke., April 11, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 26)
      - "Peace and Indo-China. "Panelists: Ralph E. Flanders, Estes Kefauver, Paul Douglas, Walter Judd., April 18, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 27)
      - "Indo-China." Panelists: William Langer, Guy Gillette, Hubert Humphrey., April 25, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape never received; Edaphone recording only)
      - "Political Issues of the Coming Campaign." Charles Lucey, moderator. Panelists: Warren Magnuson, Clarence Brown, John McCormack, Carl Curtis., May 9, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 28)
      - "Can We Achieve a Bi-partisan Foreign Policy?" Charles Lucey, moderator. Panelists: Paul Douglas, Mike Mansfield, James G. Fulton, John M. Vorys., May 16, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 29)
      - "Social Security." Ernest K. Lindley, moderator. Panelists: Robert Kean, Howard Baker, Richard Bolling, John Blatnik., May 23, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 30)
      - "Should Government Employees Give Confidential Material to Congressmen?" Ernest K. Lindley, moderator. Panelists: Estes Kefauver, H. Alexander Smith, Peter Frelinghuysen, George Mahon., June 6, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 31)
      - "Are We Holding or Losing Our Allies." Roscoe Drummond, moderator. Panelists: Guy Gillette, Craig Hosmer, Henry M. Jackson, Bailey Merrill., June 13, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 32)
      - "What Should We Do About Indo-China?" Ernest K. Lindley, moderator. Panelists: William F. Knowland, John Sherman Cooper, Mike Mansfield, James P. Richards., June 20, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 33)
      - "Power Policy" (public vs. private power sources). Ernest K. Lindley, moderator. Panelists: Carroll Reece, Charles R. Jonas, John J. Sparkman, Albert Gore., June 27, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 34)
      - US Health Care. Bryson Rash, moderator. Panelists: W. Henry Sebrell, James Watt, J. Roderick Heller, Robert H. Felix., July 4, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 35)
      - Government Housing Policy. Ernest K. Lindley, moderator. Panelists: Homer Capehart, Albert M. Cole, Albert M. Rains, Richard Bolling., July 11, 1954 (Box 27)
        (Tape 36)
    - Miscellaneous Moody Tapes
      - "This is Washington" program (report of Senator Moody to his constituents). Topic: government economy. Guest: John McClellan., circa 1951; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 27)
        (Tape 37)
      - "This is Washington" program (report of Senator Moody to his constituents). Topic: Presidential directive respecting the classification of information. Guest: William Benton., October 8, 1951; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 27)
        (Tape 38)
      - "This is Washington" program (report of Senator Moody to his constituents). Topic: Security blackout and problems of education. Guest: William F. Knowland., October 16, 1951; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 27)
        (Tape 39)
      - "This is Washington" program (report of Senator Moody to his constituents). Topic: highlights of current session of Congress., October 24, 1951; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 27)
        (Tape 40)
      - Speech at Laurium Union Hall., October 16, 1952; 7 1/2 ips; 5 in. (Box 27)
        (Tape 41)
  - Sound disks
    (16 in. discs unless otherwise indicated)
    - Blair Moody Interview
      - January 1, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16"
    - Moody Radio Newscast
      - January 27, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16"
      - February 9, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - February 16, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - February 25, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - March 3, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - March 10, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - March 17, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - (with Walter Karig), March 24, 1940; 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - (with Walter Karig), March 31, 1940; 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - April 7, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - April 14, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - April 18, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
    - Campaign broadcasts and talks
      - ("Your Washington Correspondent"), Undated; 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - Undated, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - September 20, 1940, 1 phonograph records 12 in.
      - September 27, 1940, 1 phonograph records 12 in.
      - October 3, 1940, 1 phonograph records 12 in.
      - October 10, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - October 25, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - October 31, 1940, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
    - Blair Moody Forum
      - March 9, 1947, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - July 20, 1947, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
      - July 27, 1947, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
      - December 31, 1948, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
      - January 7, 1949, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
      - January 17, 1949, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
      - Re. protection, February 6, 1949; 2 phonograph records 16 in.
    - Meet Your Congress
      - April 13, 1947, 1 phonograph records 16 in.
      - October 3, 1948, 2 phonograph records 16 in.
        (unidentified but probably MYC)
      - October 24, 1948, 3 phonograph records 12 in.
      - October 31, 1948, 3 phonograph records 12 in.
      - November 7, 1948, 3 phonograph records 12 in.
    - Miscellaneous
      - Spots, circa 1952; 2 phonograph records 10 in.
      - Radio broadcast, January 20, 1946; 1 phonograph records 12 in.
    - Various broadcasts
      - September 30, 1950, 4 phonograph records 12 in.
      - October 8, [195-], 4 phonograph records 12 in.
      - October 15 [1950], 4 phonograph records 12 in.
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    The photographs relate to Moody's career as a foreign correspondent and politician. Included also are family photographs of the Moody and Downey families.
    - Colleagues (signed photographs) (Box 28)
    - Downey, John (Civil War) (Box 28)
    - Groups, identified (Box 29)
    - Groups, unidentified (Box 28)
    - Journalist
      - Italy?, 1944 (Box 28)
      - Military (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
    - Moody, Arthur B., and family (Box 28)
    - Moody, Blair, and family, post-1940 (Box 28)
    - Moody family
      - Scotland (Box 28)
      - Unidentified (Box 28)
    - Politics (Box 28)
    - Portraits (Box 28)
    - Senator
      - Kaiser-Frazer Willow Run plant tour (Box 28)
      - Life Magazine photos (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
    - Williams, G. Mennen, with Blair Moody (Box 28)
  - Motion Pictures
    The motion pictures are of the "Meet Your Congress" television program mainly from 1953 following Moody's defeat for the Senate. Issues covered in the program include the Korean War and the incoming Eisenhower administration.
    - Meet Your Congressman Series
      - An evaluation of President Eisenhower's State of the Union Speech. Senators: Saltonstall, Ferguson, Humphrey, and Monroney, circa January, 1953; 8634-1
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
          [Restricted]
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-1, flash-flv
      - Discussion on need for US military build-up; Senators: Kennedy, Hill, Dworshak, and Morse, March 26, 1953; 8634-2
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-2, flash-flv
      - Discussion on need for US military build-up; Senators: Kennedy, Hill, Dworshak, and Morse, March 26, 1953; 8634-3
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-3, flash-flv
      - Debate on drilling for off-shore oil; Senators: Anderson, Saltonstall, Douglas, and Holland., April 16, 1953; 8634-4
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-4, flash-flv
      - Debate on drilling for off-shore oil; Senators: Anderson, Saltonstall, Douglas, and Holland., April 16, 1953; 8634-5
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-5, flash-flv
      - Peace Offensive in Korea; Senators: Flanders, Cooper, Jackson, and Mansfield., April 23, 1953; 8634-6
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-6, flash-flv
      - Solution in Asia; Senators: Smith and Douglas; Representatives: Judd and Javitz, April 30, 1953; 8634-7
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-7, flash-flv
      - Solution in Asia; Senators: Smith and Douglas; Representatives: Judd and Javitz, April 30, 1953; 8634-8
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-8, flash-flv
      - US Defense Budget; Senators: Dworshak, Case, Smathers, and Monroney, May 10, 1953; 8634-9
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-9, flash-flv
      - How to end the Korean War?; Senators: Knowland, Douglas, Long, and Morse, May 20, 1953; 8634-10
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-10, flash-flv
      - Eisenhower's Economic Program; Senators: Capehart, Bennett, Humphrey, and Kerr, May 27, 1953; 8634-11
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-11, flash-flv
      - Eisenhower's Economic Program; Senators: Capehart, Bennett, Humphrey, and Kerr, May 27, 1953; 8634-12
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-12, flash-flv
      - Air Force Budget; Senators: Duff, Ferguson, and Jackson; Representative: Yorty, June 16, 1953; 8634-13
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-13, flash-flv
      - Air Force Budget; Senators: Duff, Ferguson, and Jackson; Representative: Yorty, June 16, 1953; 8634-14
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-14, flash-flv
      - Response to Russian Initiatives in Korea; Senators: Duff, Flanders, and Robertson; Representative: Mahon, 1953; 8634-15
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-15, flash-flv
      - "Are We Ready for Red Russia,"; Senators: Duff, Flanders, and Robertson; Representative: Mahon, 1953; 8634-16
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-16, flash-flv
      - Farm Prices; Senators: Eastland, Young, Aiken, and Anderson, 1953; 8634-17
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-17, flash-flv
      - Defense Budget; Senators: McCormack and Stennis; Representatives: Judd and Hinshaw, undated; 8634-18
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-18, flash-flv
      - Defense Budget; Senators: McCormack and Stennis; Representatives: Judd and Hinshaw, undated; 8634-19
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
      - Ammunition for Korean War; Senators: Long, Morse, Robertson, and Flanders, undated; 8634-20
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-20, flash-flv
      - Military Bases Abroad; Senators: Long, Morse, Robertson, and Flanders, undated; 8634-21
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-21, flash-flv
      - Price Controls; Senators: Capehart, Maybank, and Bennett; Representative: Wolcott, undated; 8634-22
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-22, flash-flv
      - Taft-Hartley Legislation; Senators: Smith, Douglas, Ives; Representative: McConell, undated; 8634-23
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-23, flash-flv
      - Taft-Hartley Legislation; Senators: Smith, Douglas, Ives; Representative: McConell, undated; 8634-24
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-24, flash-flv
      - Action in Asia; Senators: Smith, Knowland, Douglas, and Anderson, undated; 8634-25
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-25, flash-flv
      - Truce in Korea; Senators: Knowland, Smith, Sparkman, and Douglas, undated; 8634-26
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 25 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-26, flash-flv
    - Miscellaneous FIlms
      - Interview with Senator Monroney: Discussing Budget reorganization, St. Lawrence Seaway, Anti-Corruption in Government Bill, and Employment, undated; 8634-27
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 15 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-27, flash-flv
      - Statement after being sworn in to succeed the late Senator Arthur Vandenberg, April 24, 1953; 8634-28
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 2 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-28, flash-flv
      - Prisoners of war and Korean cease fire; Senators: Long, Morse, Dworshak, and Know, undated; 8634-29
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 5 min
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 5)
        - Streaming File: 8634-29, flash-flv
Partial Index to Correspondence
Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971.
Feb. 28, 1949
Arnold, Thurman Wesley, 1891-1969.
July 30, 1940
Automobiles and the automotive industry
Feb. 20, 1952, to automobile executives concerning unemployment in Detroit
Ball, Joseph Hurst, 1905-
Nov. 4, 1941
Barkley, Alben William, 1877-1956.
July 23, 1951
Baruch, Bernard M. (Bernard Mannes), 1870-1965.
Feb. 4, 1944, Aug. 15, 1946, Aug. 16, 1946, Oct. 11, 1946, Jan. 5, 1947, Jan. 23, 1948, Jan. 24, 1948, Jan. 28, 1948; some consist of pencilled notes of Baruch on the proof sheets on Moody's books
Benton, William, 1900-1973.
Dec. 3, 1952, concerning Benton's defeat
Billington, Ray Allen, 1903-
July 30, 1951
B'nai B'rith Hillel Foundation, University of Michigan
June 18, 1951 (text of speech given by Moody at the dedication of the Hillel Foundation at the University of Michigan)
Bowles, Chester, 1901-
Apr. 1, 1946, Dec. 10, 1947, Feb. 11, 1949, June 2, 1949
Boyle, William M.
May 11, 1951
Brewster, Owen, 1884-
May 2, 1952
Brown, Muriel Buck Humphrey
May 27, 1952
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
June 9, 1934, June 25, 1943
Brownell, Herbert, 1904-
Dec. 4, 1948
Butler of Saffron Walden, Richard Austen Butler, Baron, 1902-
Oct. 26, 1949, Feb. 10, 1950
Byrnes, James Francis, 1879-1972.
June 1, 1939, Jan. 11, 1940
Cain, Harry Pulliam, 1906-
Jan. 14, 1942, Apr. 21, 1951
Capehart, Homer E. (Homer Earl), 1897-1979.
Jan. 25, 1952
Childs, Marquis William, 1903-
Jan. 17, 1952
Clapper, Raymond, 1892-1944.
July 8, 1941, Nov. 14, 1941 [enclosure], Nov. 11, 1941 [In book correspondence]
Clardy, Kit Francis, 1892-
July 20, 1951, Aug. 31, 1951, Sept. 10, 1951, Dec. 13, 1951
Connally, Tom, 1877-1963.
Feb. 11, 1952
Connelly, Matthew J 1907-
Mar. 13, 1952
Corcoran, Thomas Gardiner, 1900-
June 5, 1952
Couzens, Frank, 1902-1950.
Oct. 28, 1934, July 22, 1935, Oct. 16, 1935
Cripps, Richard Stafford, Sir, 1889-1952.
Aug. 11, 1948
Daniels, Jonathan, 1902-
July, 6 1951
Davis, Elmer Holmes, 1890-1958.
Oct. 10, 1942
Dean, Gordon E., 1905-1958.
May 1, 1952, enclosing memo of American Newspaper Editors Committee on freedom of Information
Detroit, Mich. - Race question
June 12, 1942, June 23, 1943 and Aug. 3, 1943, of L. G. Lenhard on Negroes in Detroit
Diggs, Charles C., 1922-
Dec. 13, 1951
Dingell, John D. (John David), 1894-1955.
Feb. 16, 1934, Feb. 22, 1934, Apr. 23, 1951, June 13, 1951, Sept. 16, 1952
DiSalle, Michael V. (Michael Vincent), 1908-
Oct. 8, 1951
Dondero, George Anthony, 1883-1968.
Dec. 9, 1943
Douglas, Paul Howard, 1892-
Jan. 14, 1953, also comments on Douglas as a possible presidential nominee in the pre-convention period 1952
Downey, Sheridan, 1884-1961.
Feb. 27, 1942
Dulles, Allen Welsh, 1893-1969.
June 27, 1951
Eaton, Cyrus Stephen, 1883-
Feb. 5, 1944
Eggleston, Arthur Francis, 1890-
Oct. 4, 1938
Eisenhower, Milton Stover, 1899-
Nov. 22, 1934
Farley, James Aloysius, 1888-
Oct. 6, 1950, Oct. 9, 1950, May 31, 1951, Sept. 27, 1951
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
Jan. 23, 1948, Mar. 26, 1948, Apr. 25, 1951; also letter, Apr. 21, 1952, of Charles Murphy, White House assistant concerning Ferguson
Ford, Henry, 1917-1987.